Welcome babies to my stream.
Come on, wife
I'll always support you.
Except for dancing
What else do you want to see?"
My wife looks great
I enjoy everything.
As long as you give me rockets
You can see anything
Love you, wife.
Lousy phone
Sweetie, wait for me, husband.
This bastard
Soul Culture: Bunny girl host is cute and sexy.
Where is the anchor from?
Be your own sun: Thanks for your support.
Thanks for the gifts and support.
Thanks all for the courtesy, husband.
Xu Jie: Boring, let's talk privately!
Are you annoyed?
Who is that man, Jiang Qingqing?
What does it have to do with you?
Is Xu Jie's wealthy second gen?
Ah
So what?
Am I doomed to be poor with you forever?
Let's end it
You can't give me the life I need.
Qingqing
I was wrong, I was wrong
I shouldn't shout at you.
Will not lose your temper with you again
Can you forgive me?
Don't break up with me, Qingqing."
I don't care about you
Don't bother me in the future
Jiang Qingqing Xu Jie
You dog man and woman
Go to death
Sorry, no line provided to shorten.
A good dog won't block the way.
Move aside now
The young master finally found you
Sick
Who's your young boss?
Wrong person.
I'm Hu Yun.
Your father's personal butler
This time I came to you
My father
Since that was abandoned after my mother and son.
I have no relation to him.
Master left you long ago.
也有难处。
Who the hell has no hardships
Just because of that so-called hardship
He left his wife and kids.
He has known for years
Me and my mother
How did you get here?
The master will inherit the family.
It's their only option.
Master's pocket money for you.
This card
able to get you around the country
All get best treatment
It shows status.
The master said
Before he completely inherited the first family
Please don't be public
First family
That's it
Control the world's economic core
Super big family
yes
Young master, trouble? Come to me.
我们家族解决不了的困难没有
Son
To give
This month's living costs
Take it
Six hundred seems a bit low
Mom can still earn more
You're at school.
Just eat and drink
Auntie
Rovita is at school.
Food and drink are good.
And not only that
He still has money to tip girls.
I don’t get some people
What kind of big-tailed wolf is pretending to be here
No young master's life.
He also got the young master's disease
It's really shameless
Don't listen to her
I have money now
I'll take you shopping for a few clothes.
Pick what you want; I'll buy it for you.
What are you talking about?
Casual clothes here
No two or three hundred
We are a high-end brand
Clothes don’t cost over two or three hundred.
What do you mean?
It means that you pee
Take care of yourself
Not just anyone
You can come to our store to consume
Let's go now
Let's go
Today, I'll see it.
What's in the store?
I can't afford it
I really look down on you.
Obviously a poor student
Okay, don't learn
I only want to learn dressing.
Are you eligible?
You repeat
Too lazy to deal with you.
Get out of here
Leave now or I'll call security.
What's going on
What are you arguing about?
This person insisted on coming to the store to make trouble
was about to blast him out
Whose card is this?
Any questions
Sir
Is this your card?
Well
Meet the heir of the first family
Meet the first family heir
This is not just one
Regular bank card
Shut up
Your performance this month is gone
Make tea for them now.
You know me
No资格。
I'm abroad
I have met the chairman
Very respectful to an old man
He is in his hands
There is one
Cards that are exactly like you
Didn't expect this card
It surprisingly has big deterrence.
My dad's family seems strong.
No
You are in the store today
All spending
I'll pay for it
Just be
Sorry for the trouble.
Not welcome here
Don't stay
How dare a small shop not welcome you
Even our whole group
I don't dare to go against you
This is our group's gold card
With this card
Under our group
Any mall
All are free
Please also ask your lord not to remember the villain's faults
Yes
I'll take your apology.
Don't forget to come to KTV to work at night
I've promised your goddess.
Make me happy.
I'll get her to top rank.
Ah
Your goddess
How is it in front of me
Please, please
Hahahahaha
行啊，徐大少
I'll watch your show.
Wife
Drink tea
Who is your wife?
Didn't I say it?
If you help me rush to the top of the list
I'll consider being your girlfriend again
Qingqing
Wait two more days for me.
In two days, I’ll get my pay.
I'll help you make the list right away, okay?"
etc
I don't have time to wait for you.
You waste
I can't count on it
Qingqing
Jiang Qingqing
Don't look down on young and poor.
I'm here
、
Yo is still Brother Xu's atmosphere
Sister-in-law's list is stable
As expected of Xu family's eldest.
The shot is so generous
How can it be
How am I now?
It's eleventh on the list
Brother Xu, you have to help me
Don't worry, I'll give you another one.
Yo-yo-yo不好
My sister-in-law was squeezed out of the top ten of the list again
What
Brother Xu
You can help me
If you put me in the top ten
I can do whatever you say
The top ten live broadcast room rewards
Each one is more than one hundred thousand
This week's list is forgotten
Go back and rest first
All right
That person will go back and wait for you
You must come
Just go
Who else do I think?
Isn't this the dog licking Luo Wei?
Come on
Take the money your master gave you
Get out of here
Don't roll yet
Give you ten minutes
Get out
Oops
You poor ghost asked me to get out
Tell you
Lao Tzu is a super VIP here
Super VIP right?
I have to show you today
What is a real super VIP
Pass it on
All consumption today
I will pay for it
All the wine is casual
But
Some dogs are never allowed inside
Pass it on
All consumption today
I will pay for it
All the wine is casual
But
Such a high-end occasion
I always feel like some dogs
It's an eyesore here
The accounts have been cleared
Young Master Luo Wei paid 500,000 yuan
Blast him out for me
Get out
How can it be
Where did you get the money?
Don't think that a few stinky money is amazing
I'm sorry
I just think I'm amazing
You think that's it
You owe me
It's just the beginning
I'm telling you
I'm not short of money
I am not welcome here
I'm not uncommon
Let's go
Slow down
What do you want to do
If I remember correctly
Master Xu hasn't paid the bill yet
You spend a total of 3,870 yuan
Isn't it just 3,000 yuan?
What I have is money
Is there any money?
Don't be here if you don't have money
How can it be
I was still there just now
The live broadcast room swiped 30,000 yuan
Hey Dad
Why is there no money in my bank card?
Don't talk to me
The patrol knocks on the door outside
What's wrong, Dad
You cheating thing
It's out there
What kind of person did you offend
Your father is going to be killed by you."
Comrade police officer
Master Xu, I still have some money
Let's get out quickly
Hey
What do you want to do?
Master Xu
Just broke my bottle of wine
I haven't given the money yet."
Isn't it just a bottle of wine?
How much can it be worth?
I will pay you
Well, it's really refreshing
The Macallan '82 Collector's Edition
Pay
What
It seems that our eldest young master Xu
No money to settle the bill
Let him be obedient
What do you TM want to do?
You dare to touch me
The Xu family will not let you go
Are you still young?
It can be here
Work slowly to pay off debts
You wait for me
How can you make me wait."
Master Xu doesn't know yet
made a phone call
Your father now
It has been because of illegal fundraising
was arrested
Face him
It will be an endless prison disaster
There is no family
You talk nonsense, you talk nonsense
On one's mind
This is your life
The best red wine ever drunk
Take away
bastard
Where is Brother Xu
Luo Wei
How can you drink here at night
Can you be a little more mature?
It turned out that I thought you loved me so much
Willing to work here to support me
It turns out you're just messing around here
What happened to me with my own money
It's better than that Xu Jie
Use his old money to be strong
Is it
You use your own money
I didn't dare to admit it if I stole money
Your mother should be ashamed of you
What do you mean
Luo Wei
You are really thick-skinned
I was really blind
You stole Zhao Huan's money
Forget about buying clothes for your mother
You're still drinking here
Zhao Huan's family is rich
But she is not obliged to come to your rescue
You know
Hey
You thief
How dare you steal this girl's money
No wonder Qingqing dumped you
People like you
Not worthy of a girlfriend at all
Who stole your money
You explain the words to me clearly
I don't bother to tell you
You're still fooling around outside
I'm really sorry, classmate
But I believe in my son
He didn't mean to
Okay, okay, don't say it
Take care of your son
It's very annoying
I didn't steal money
stole money to buy clothes for your mother
I still don't admit my mistake
You say a few words
I'll settle the score for you when I go back
Mom, believe me, I didn't steal money
actually stole money to buy clothes for his mother
This poor filial piety
I ask you how much you have lost
What's wrong with two thousand?
If I tell you
My mother's dress
More than two thousand dollars
Can you prove that I didn't take it?
What the hell are you trying to say?
Just like you
Thousands of dollars of clothes
I want to say that
You can't afford this dress for my mother
You don't have that much money STANDING either
What do you pretend?
Your mother's dress
If I can't afford it
I'll give you back the two thousand dollars
I slapped myself again
Okay
See for yourself
What do you see?"
Don't be afraid that we will support you
Luo Wei didn't steal my money
I made a mistake myself
Oh Mom, where did you get so much money?
DC
You sold blood
There is no time for me to draw blood
Come on a beautiful little girl
said it was your classmate
Lend me two thousand yuan
Hey you boy
Is it secretly in love?
No, no
OUSTANDING
What does that person look like?
He is beautiful and watery
Oh, the figure is good
There is about 1.7 meters
When I saw her
Wearing a pair of sports leggings
Anyway, you kid is blessed
1.7 meters
Sports Leggings:
Then it can only be her
Hey Yang Huan
Wait a minute
Luo Wei
Oh my mother's business
Thank you for that
Why don't I treat you to dinner."
No
Oh, you can choose the location
You really want to thank me
Then let's eat the cafeteria
Canteen hey
You stinky dick
It is also worthy of inviting Huanhuan to dinner
Others invite girls to dinner
That's all in fine dining restaurants
You are in the cafeteria
Are you a man?
I eat in the cafeteria, and I am happy
What does it matter to you
I invite you to the evening
Kebin International
Whatever you want to eat
Do you want to be with me?
My young master can pity you."
Take you to see the world
So that you know
between you and us
How big is the gap?
Kaibin International is, right?
Oh, it's the evening rush hour now
Why hasn't this Luo Wei come yet?
If you take a taxi, it will be blocked
Luo Wei here
Sorry for the traffic jam
It's late
Yo brothers
It costs a lot of money
Okay, you can say a few words
Where did you get in?
You can enter through the main entrance
Hello
Please show your reservation information
What
Sorry sir
We at Kaibin International are members-based
Isn't it just a member?
I'll just give you the money
Non-members need to book one year in advance
Hey, I have to go in today
The annual consumption reaches 10 million
to join
You can't enter Mr
I really want to pretend not to know him
Why don't I change places?"
Now we can go inside
Please come in, sir
If you are a member, please go through the member channel
Quality
I want you to pretend to be my boyfriend
I know it's embarrassing for you
You have to feel that the money is small
You say the number
E SES
I accepted the card
Forget the money
The address is sent to me
I'll go tomorrow
ES
Young master
The gift you ordered is ready
I asked you to prepare one for me
A low-key gift with connotation
You prepared this for me
Enough to explode
It's so early
Beautiful women make an appointment
Of course, come early
Come in
This is the living room
Over there is a study and fitness room
Usually Su Li and me
Worked out in the gym together
Will Su Li come again in a while?
will come
I asked her to come later
Just let her
Help me prepare something
Ten
Oh, let's go, let's go
What are you going to do?
You promised me
Protect me throughout the process today
I'll do what you say
Luo Wei: Can you be lighter?
I would like to listen to your arrangements
No one dares to ask me to apologize yet
THE
Luo Wei was careful
ss you
You let go of me
Help me
Where is the miss?
The young lady changed her dress in the room
Rovi Lowe
Can you lighten it?
Excuse me
This is the first time I have encountered this kind of thing
You lighten it, you hurt me."
Oh, I'm sorry
It's almost good, it's almost good
Yang Huan, what are you doing inside
Tang... Tang Shao
Who did you put in?"
It's all in Yang Huan's bedroom
What are you shouting?
What are you doing?
I just let Rovi
Zip it up for me
Are you okay?"
He's my boyfriend
We've been together for a month
I will never marry you
The woman who dares to mess with me Tang Shao
You wait for me
This is
I give you a birthday present
Oh Yang Huan
This is my birthday present for you
Happy birthday
Thank you, thank you
Yang Huan
This is me abroad
Specially customized natural colored diamonds for you
Styles and styles
I made it for you
Do you like it
This gift is too expensive
I can't take it
No matter how precious it is, it is not as precious as yours
Wow
These 100,000 gem-grade white diamonds
Only one colored diamond can appear
This is particularly precious
Young Master Tang is really generous
Miss Yang is so happy
What are you giving?"
apple
It means he cares about me
Safe and healthy
Hahaha
An apple represents good health
Such a birthday gift
You also sent it
Luo Wei
Such a birthday gift
You also sent it
Ten
This is me
A birthday gift for Miss Yang
Just this broken box
Give me the colored diamonds I gave to Yang Huan
Is it still a valuable gift?
Hahahaha
Isn't this just a broken stone?
You gave it to me
Not as good as an apple
You see clearly
Wei
It can be more expensive than diamonds
I said don't believe Luo Wei
Yang Huan, you are really too
Find someone to pretend to be a boyfriend
Don't look for a rich one
Don't get out of here
Yang Huan trusts you so much
What did you give away?"
Yes, get out of here
How about Miss Yang
Now you know
With me
It's the best choice
Miss
Rowe asked me to leave this to you
Luo Wei didn't ask for money
What is Huanhuan looking at?
Miss
Sister is back
It's nothing more than a stone
This is
My sister knows this thing
This thing has a price and no market
It is the most expensive metal in the world
It is extremely helpful in treating cancer
It is in the world now
Treat cancer is one of the few
Advanced means
The annual output is only 0. 25 g
1 gram costs at least 3, 0 million
No wonder when Luo Wei sent me
Say wish me good health
Oh no, I misunderstood him
What is Luo Wei?
Just a poor DS
Dare to oppose me
You are not participating
Miss Yang's birthday party?
Why are you so angry
Go
Bring my notebook
I didn't expect this thing
It's really invincible
ThinkPad
Although I don't know
How did you get it?
You're screwed
Play tricks with me
You don't deserve it
You mean
Doesn't Yang Huan like you quite a bit?"
I made her hate you for the rest of my life
Young master, your trick
NAPOLEON
I'm sorry for what happened to Luo Wei today
I want to apologize to you in person
NAPOLEON
TH
FD is OK
NAPOLEON
A truly upper-class person
THE
Not only must it have strength and connotation
I also want the prime minister to be able to hold the boat in his belly
Engineering
NA
THA
Engineering
HE NAPOLEON
THE
This handsome guy doesn't care about her
Well, I'll be right away
Long wait
I misunderstood you today
I'm sorry, Luo Wei
E SES didn't eat at the party either
Otherwise, treat me to a late-night snack
PtE SES I will forgive you
-2020
Let's go
Respect you
For today's events
I apologize to you
Luo Wei
Thank you
What are you polite to me?"
Didn't you help me once
Hey
Yang Huan
Oops
Haha laughed to death
I don't know how to hide
You okay
Zhao Huan
You did it on purpose
Are you addicted to bullying?
Thank you
I'm fine
What does it have to do with me
It was she who was careless
Walk without looking at the road
How can you blame me
What nonsense
I clearly saw that it was you
Apologize
What do you call your dog?
I didn't mean to
Ah
It's not intentional, is it?
You dare to push me
I didn't mean to
You wait for me
Uncle
I was bullied
He also pushed me
My parents have never done anything to me
Who is so bold
How dare I bully you
It's Luo Wei from our college
It was me he bullied me
Uncle will definitely help you get justice
Thank you, uncle
I know that you love Huanhuan the most
Luo Wei You wait for me
Bully Miss Ben
It will definitely make you look good
You want to fire me
He was not convinced
Even if you have good academic performance
What can be done?
Your BL classmate's business
It seriously affects the reputation of the college
I serve as the Director of Instruction
You have the right to fire a BL like this
Yes
Since it's you
First of all, there is no distinction between black and white
Make black white
Then let's take a look
Whoever fires whom first
Yo
How dare you threaten me
Luo Shao
You finally contacted me
When will I see you
Luo Shao
You finally contacted me
When will I see you
Just now
I'm here
Office of the Director of Instruction
Come here
My people will be there soon
Please start your performance
Didn't you hear Lao Tzu educating students?
Dare to bully my precious niece
Even if the king of heaven is coming
I will definitely fire you
Principal
What wind blew you
Master Luo
Excuse me
As soon as I received your call
Immediately put down the work in hand
Just came over
It's not late
Principal
You're late
5 minutes ago
I was expelled from school
What
Who dares to fire you
I abandoned him
Oops
Who else could it be?
Of course, it manages our students
Teaching director
you
Pack up your things immediately and get out
Principal
I know I was wrong
Just spare me this time."
It's not me who makes you angry
It's Master Luo
Luo classmates
No, young master
I was confused for a moment
You have a large number of adults
Don't let the school expel me
You rely on yourself as the director of instruction
At school JG JS
S SHL
ZW ZF
Have you ever thought about today's results?
If I had known, why should I have done it today?
It's all you ZY YD
Master Luo
Our school education investment
The principal can rest assured
I'll ask the housekeeper to contact you
You walk slowly
Yo
Isn't this Luo Dashao?
It is actually condescending to be noble
Come to the cafeteria for dinner
Where do I go to eat?"
It seems unnecessary
Report it to a dog
It's okay if you don't want to pay attention to me
I'm waiting to see Luo Shao who is booming NB
How to harm your beloved woman
Family P people W's
I'm warning you
Dare to move Yang Huan
I let you have no place to bury yourself
Hey
I will accompany you to visit the supermarket in the morning
You are too energetic
Okay, okay, let's go
You buy these
I want to bring Rovi a breakfast
What
Luo Wei
What are you doing, Yang Huan
You won't like it
That stinky boy
Oh, okay, okay
Let's go
I didn't expect this to be famous
Female president Yang Le
Even using fake geoiforium ore
FF JZ
Hey
What did you say
The Yang Group utilizes fake geonium ore
FF JZ
No way
This is all reported in the news
Yang's Group
At the press conference
Utilize fake geollium ore FF JZ
Now
It has entered the trial stage
Hey Yang Huan
Wake up Yang Huan
Yang Huan, you are awake
Luo Wei
How are you here
Oh, it's a coincidence
I happened to pass by a convenience store
I saw you and Su Li
The Yang family is going to do something big
I want to hurry back."
Calm down
You need to rest now
The giranite was given to me by you
I let you before that
Apologize for doing my boyfriend's business
But why are you?
I'm going back
You step aside
Yang Huan, listen to my explanation
Not what you think
rest assured
I will definitely find out the truth of the matter
It will definitely not let the Yang family be in trouble
Yesterday, Yang's Group was released
Because of the use of fake geollium ore FF JZ
The Yang Group utilizes fake kernium ore FF JZ
The current package has entered the trial stage
Sued by a large number of investors
The Yang Group utilizes fake kernium ore FF JZ
The current package has entered the trial stage
It has now entered the trial stage
The Yang Group utilizes fake kernium ore FF JZ
The current package has entered the trial stage
The gibronium I gave you cannot be fake
No one dares to sell our family fakes
I'll investigate now
I already know who did it
It's the young master
Whoever it is
I will definitely let him die without a place to be buried."
Miss Yang
Aren't you usually very arrogant?"
Always looked down on me
Now you have to be obedient
Kneel down in front of me
As long as Miss Yang
Coaxed me to be happy
This chisel
I would like 50 million
Sell it to your Yang family at a low price
But it's okay if you don't want to
After all, your Yang family
And it's not just your daughter
I've liked your sister Yang Huan for a long time
No
Please let Huan Huan go
I'll do what you say
You rebellious son
Who the hell have you offended
Dad, why are you here?"
Fast
Give Luo a little compensation
I have long said don't touch the Yang family
Right now
Ready to take on my fury
Luo Wei, don't be impulsive
I will return the rongium to the Yang family now."
It's late
After today
I want the Tang family to disappear in Binshi
It's all our fault
Please let us live
I want to admit my mistake
Yes
Go kneel down and kowtow to Yang Le
Knocked to Yang Le
I am willing to let you go
This matter can't be left alone
I want to make Luo Wei pay for his blood
useless
The strength behind them is too great
We have no chance of winning
Is this the Tang family?
It's really too many comfortable days
It's really too comfortable
There is no blood at all
Where did the nameless junior come from
also dare to teach our Tang family a lesson
Tang Wei
Remember who it was back then
Help you establish the Tang family
This is
It doesn't matter who I am
I want to ruin Luo Wei's reputation
And do as I command
Our Tang family is up and down
I would like to listen to your arrangements
Brother Yang
In the final analysis, I have no way to discipline them
Drunkenness and promiscuity
I brought him here today
I apologize to you
I'm sorry Uncle Yang
I sincerely apologize to you
Dad
How did you come out to party?"
What are you doing here
You Uncle Tang
Know the fault of poor discipline
I'm here to make amends for your sister
No, you don't
Keep saying
Come and apologize to my sister
But he only brought a blue and white porcelain
It's really insincere
Huanhuan is right
It's not just a lack of consideration
You brought a fake
Say what
A ceramic imitation of the Tang Dynasty
-2020
OLEO I
A ceramic imitation of the Tang Dynasty
OLE OP
The workmanship is so delicate
At first glance, it is modern craftsmanship
OLEO A
Uncle Tang, you won't be able to see it
ES
Even if it's a fake
It's not an ordinary street stall
They can be compared
What do you know
I don't understand
But what about me today
also brought a gift to Uncle Yang
It's nothing
It's just a piece of meat Ganoderma
That's what the news mentions
FPt E POLEON
NAPO LA
F PtES
Let's start from scratch
I miss you so much
Okay, where are you?
I'm waiting for you in my hotel room
Luo Wei
I know you're still angry with me
I don't ask you to forgive me
But we're still friends, right?
Am I good-looking?
I just broke someone else's bottle of wine
People asked me to compensate
But I don't have that much money
Can you help me?"
30,008
You feel like yourself
Is it worth the price?
I don't want to see you again
What do you mean
But you have to give it if you don't give it today
Otherwise
I'll call the police now
Say you forced me
Played all night
Just for this
How did it work?
It's done
I looked at Luo Wei with my own eyes
was taken away
Even if I can't kill you this time
I have to make you suffer a little too
Luo Shao I'm really sorry
How is it possible to force one
Cheap bar marketing
Never mind
As long as I can prove my innocence
I don't want to
Let our family be jealous
After investigation
The biggest suspicion
It should be Jiang Qingqing
But she shouldn't
The mastermind behind the scenes
Isn't this Master Luo?"
Why did you commit a crime?
It's the first time I've seen you
Someone took the initiative to send it to the door
Ms. Jiang Qingqing and Mr. Tang Chuan
Now we doubt you two
Suspected WG FB
Please cooperate with our investigation
Come with us
OM
Hey
Luo Shao
It's been a long time since I last saw you
Tang Chuan
How is Huanhuan's mobile phone here?
You are looking for Huanhuan
She's at my house
But it's a pity
Huanhuan will fall asleep here
Luo Shao wants to pick up people in person
Tang Chuan, I warn you
If you dare to move a hair
I will let your entire Tang family be buried
Luo Wei
You have done good things to me again and again
I'm going to make you pay
Today the Yang family and you
Don't run away from anyone
Tang Chuan
You let her go
You can do as much as you want
Luo Wei
I just wanted to get the Yang family
But now
I changed my mind
Aren't you crazy
Don't touch her
I am just for you
Watching his woman be WN
Hmph
Let her go
Luo Wei
You also have today
Hahaha
Looking for death
Joy
Let me go
BIRTH
Young master
How did you find this?
I still remember it in the young master's hand
Is it a pitch black dragon king card?
There are special chips in it
It can be positioned by satellite
What should the young master do?
Leave it to the inspection
It seems
The Tang family is really useless